

Daniel Beihaghi

Sales Specialist/ The Challenger

With more than five years of experience in the sales industry, I have acquired extensive knowledge in sales, corporate branding, and business acumen. I am a highly motivated and dynamic individual who has consistently achieved excellent results in my previous roles through diligent and purposeful work. Colleagues have described me as positive and charismatic, while my managers have consistently highlighted my reliability and strong work ethic.

daniel.beihaghi@gmail.com



+46723007444



Malmö, Sverige



in linkedin.com/in/danbei

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Manager Zetes

02/2023 - Present, Malmö, Sweden Zetes is an innovative supply chain technology company Hit and exceeded department KPIs by 70% for the first 3 months

Sales and budget responsibility for Zetes' products, services and solutions to increase efficiency and operational quality within the customer's material handling process and/or data flows. Customer responsibility for both existing accounts and new customer processing in the warehouse, transport & retail logistics segments in the Nordic region.

Contact: Hampus Due Hansson -+46701485249

Global Account Executive Jobtip

01/2022 - 07/2022,

Gothenburg, Sweden

Jobtip is the Nordics most prominent tech company within HR with offices in Gothenburg, Oslo, Gdansk and Cleveland.

Achievements/Tasks

Led a project together with a consultant to launch their new SaaS solution, created new routines in CRM, identified potential customers, held workshops and trainings both internally and externally to larger companies with a focus on creating new organisational teams from scratch. In addition, I was responsible for the entire sales process with companies of 1000+ employees.

Contact :Ali Farshid -+46737690100

Cloud Sales Specialist Telavox

01/2019 - 01/2022.

Malmö. Sweden

Telavox is a telecommunications software company with more than 20 years of experience enabling rewarding conversations.

Achievements/Tasks

- Started as a BDR and within 3 months I was managing my own accounts. Managed the entire sales cycle and had appointments delivered by the BDR team. On top of that, I trained our customer success team on how to upsell and keeping the customer from "churning"/leaving using the challenger sales methodology.
- Results: 128 and 114% against budget and the highest margin on my business in the country.

Contact: Patrik Johansson -+46720504696

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Kristianstad University (2015 - 2016)

Banking & Finance

LANGUAGES

Swedish

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Persian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Boxing

Travel

Music

Food

UPDATED EXPERIENCE

Account Executive
Billetto, Copenhagen, Denmark

April 2024 – Present

- Responsible for managing and expanding the customer portfolio.
- Oversees the entire sales cycle, from prospecting to closing deals.
- Drives growth by identifying new business opportunities.
- Collaborates with marketing and product teams.